但如果人们发现 他这么做是为了出名…
But if people find out that he's doing this for personal fame...
…他们会对英雄失去信心 就像之前一样
...they'll lose faith in heroes just like before.
先锋还只是小问题
Booster is the least of our problems.
我不太习惯出席这种场合
I've never been comfortable in a suit and tie.
我比较习惯待在实验室或家里
I'm more at home in the lab.
我认得他 是泰德寇德
- Hey, I recognize him. - It's Ted Kord.
寇德企业 寇德企业
- Kord Industries. - Kord Industries.
所以我成立了寇德企业 是中西部的军火业龙头
- That's why I founded Kord Industries. - The Blackwater of the Midwest.
先前他的卡车被黄金先锋挡下时 有一项高科技产品不见了
High-tech device went missing when one of his trucks crashed into Booster Gold.
寇德声称他的公司 是单纯的科技公司
Kord claims that his company is all about technology.
但是他们的研发项目…
Their research and development includes many things...